Jacob Noah

Full Stack Developer

SKILLS

Languages

- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- PHP
- Python

Frameworks

- React, Next
- Vue, Nuxt
- Angular
- Node.js
- Express, Hapi, Loopback
- Laravel, Symfony
- Django

Personal Profile

Full Stack developer with more than 8 years of experience in JavaScript and PHP. I have strong analytical skills and take great care in communicating with clients to find the right solution for their needs.

I value openness and transparency a great deal so that I can understand why decisions are made in a certain way and can voice any doubts early on. My core competency lies in complete end-end management of a new website development project, and I am seeking opportunities to build websites and mobile apps from the ground up for you or your business

Work Experience

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Self-Employed Feb 2021 - present

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Seavus

May 2019 - Jul 2021

- Upgraded a powerful SaaS which using VueJS and Vuex, Vuetify framework
- Developed headless CMS with React.js, Node.js and Strapi
- Led a team of engineers working on computer vision R&D projects.
- Built the CMS, CRM using Vue/Nuxt and Laravel
- Wrote the front-end web app from scratch using React and Redux to significantly improve the bounce rate after the initial launch of the site.
- Promoted DevOps practices adoption, implemented transparent deployment pipeline with Jira, Git, Jenkins, Docker, and Azure.
- Worked on MERN projects (Rect/Node framework) as an engineer.
- Implemented load and performance testing with JMeter, database performance optimization

Jacob Noah

Full Stack Developer

Contact Details

Address:

Sarajevo, Federation of Bosnia and Herzegovina Email:

jacob.noah.jnn@gmail.com Linkedin:

linkedin.com/in/jacob-noah

Education

University of East Sarajevo

Master's Degree, Computer Science 2007 - 2012

Work Experience

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Eton Digital Ltd. Sept 2016 - May 2019

- Databases, Google Maps, laravel, php, wordpress, chrome extension.
- Provided coding services to 40 clients from various industries such as
- telecommunications, e-commerce, website design, healthcare and finance.
- Collaborated closely with software developers and website designers.
- Oriented clients on program maintenance and troubleshooting procedures.
- Provided maintenance services to clients for 3 months.
- Conducted marketing campaigns to promote Whiteside Programmers.

Technologies: Laravel, React, Vue, Angular, Node, Python, AWS Serverless, NoSOL

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Squareball Digital Jan 2013 - Aug 2016

- Upgraded architecture of an enterprise clothing platform Node, MongoDB, Firebase.
- Developed headless CRM by using Strapi, Node and React
- Redesigned database MySQL to MongoDB
- Developed price analysis platform depend on Price api and Google Merchant api with React and Node